# **ADI VRSKIC**

## adivrskic.dev | adivrskic123@gmail.com | 678 230 6936 | Kennesaw, GA

#### **PROFILE**

Several years of front and back end development experience, building and enhancing both large and small scale eCommerce websites and applications, including integration of flooring visualization solutions and large scale redesigns. Professional knowledge using multiple different web development frameworks and libraries, especially React. Solid grasp of software development lifecycles, with experience in Agile environments. Seeking challenges to improve current skill set as well as to develop new skills.

### **LANGUAGES & SKILLS**

- HTML5, CSS3, Vanilla JS, SEO best practices, Accessibility, Mobile-first, Git 6 years
- Front-End: React & Vue.js 4 years
- Back-End: Python & Node.js 3 years
- Use of both SQL & NoSQL databases 2 years
- Practical eCommerce & CMS knowledge Shopify, Squarespace & Bloomreach 3 years
- APIs, CosmosDB & Cloud Functions with Microsoft Azure 2 years

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Software Engineer - React**

2021-present

#### **Visionaire Partners - Remote**

- Implemented SEO improvements on product pages leading to increased traffic and revenue for the Homedepot website.
- Assisted in architecting and implementing a large scale, modern redesign on product pages throughout the Homedepot website experiences.

Programmer – Web 2018-2021

## Mohawk Industries - Calhoun, Ga & Kennesaw, GA

- Implementation and integration of a flooring visualizer React application, used to preview and test flooring products on PC or mobile devices, on multiple websites.
- Use of Microsoft Azure Storage and CosmosDB to upload and store thousands of products and use of Azure Cloud Functions for CRUD operations to enhance user experience on all built sites.
- Creation of an Electron app using the existing flooring visualizer API to generate over one thousand high quality room scenes daily, which are used for marketing purposes.
- Trained and mentored associate developers on small projects and tasks using the latest front end technologies and frameworks.
- Focus on mobile-first, accessibility-first, SEO friendly modern development practices using the Google Chrome Lighthouse tool.

#### **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Science, Computer Science – Kennesaw State University

2013-2018

- Interactive game and app development including a virtual reality online classroom mobile application.
- Functioning forum website development including a complete user registration system and the ability for users to post and reply to messages in various topics.